The vitelline vesicle serves as an initial reservoir of nutritional information.
卵黄囊，一开始就像一个营养信息的储备库。
It is present, but at a certain point, the system grows so extensively within it
它在那里，但在某个时刻，系统在其中生长得如此之大，
that, in fact, it undergoes relative regression.
以至于它实际上相对退化了。
This vitelline vesicle will merge with the embryonic pedicle
这个卵黄囊将与胚胎柄结合，
and together they will form the umbilical cord.
两者将形成脐带。
Thus, it is not a mere abrupt disappearance,
所以，它并不是真的像“噗”的一声那样，
but rather the encompassing field of global influence, if you will,
而是周围的整体吸吮场，如果你愿意的话，
but not strictly within the vitelline vesicle itself.
但不在你的卵黄囊内部。
A portion of this vitelline vesicle will be integrated into the intestinal system.
这个卵黄囊的一部分将被整合到肠道系统中。
However, the remnant of this yolk sac will be incorporated into the
但这个卵黄囊的遗迹将被重新纳入
embryonic pedicle.
胚胎柄。
It will be integrated to constitute the entirety of the umbilical cord.
它将被整合以形成整个脐带。
Thus, there is significant growth, and this growth will be particularly pronounced at the cerebral level.
因此，有一个非常重要的生长，大脑的生长将非常重要。
Nevertheless, the digestive system appears to develop later.
然而，消化系统似乎发展得更晚。
But fundamentally, it is more precocious, as it is the system that initiates the primary influence.
但从根本上说，它更早，因为它带来了影响。
However, we are initially dependent on the maternal digestive system.
但我们首先依赖于母亲的消化系统。
In its emergence, the glandular system appears prior to the nervous system.
在出现方面，腺体系统出现在神经系统之前。
This implies that without a functional digestive system, viability is compromised.
这意味着如果我没有消化系统，我就会死。
Similarly, the absence of a glandular system is incompatible with life.
如果我没有腺体系统，我就会死。
Conversely, the initial absence of a fully developed nervous system is not immediately critical for early embryonic survival.
如果我没有神经系统，那也不是太严重。
The glandular system holds paramount importance.
腺体系统非常非常重要。
I will briefly discuss the hypothalamo-hypophyseal axis.
我将简单地谈谈下丘脑-垂体轴。
thyroid, adrenal, and even, to some extent, gonadal.
甲状腺、肾上腺，甚至还有一点性腺。
This is an exceedingly crucial axis
这是一个非常非常重要的轴，
and we will briefly examine the relationship between the thyroid and the
我们将稍微研究一下甲状腺和肾上腺之间的关系，
adrenal glands
肾上腺
in conjunction with the hypothalamus. We are entirely regulated
与下丘脑相关。我们完全受制于
and women, even more so, are governed by hormones.
尤其是女性，受荷尔蒙的影响。
They are, 'metaphorically speaking,' influenced by the lunar cycle, operating on a 28-day rhythm. To address a
她们依赖于月亮，打个引号，28天。治疗一个
hormonal system
荷尔蒙系统
in the plane
在计划中
it often involves releasing phases of congestion.
通常是释放充血阶段。
one may experience phases of congestion
你可能会有充血阶段
at the cervical level
在颈部
at the thymic level
在胸腺水平
or even at the hepatic level
或者甚至在肝脏水平
this is where one can intervene
这是我们可以采取行动的地方
and then it's about understanding the mechanism
然后是理解机制
of systems' biofeedback
系统的生物反馈
and then I will integrate all this into the digestive system
然后我将把所有这些放回消化系统
with the sites of resorption
与吸收部位
and how it manifests in the
以及它如何在
duodenal system, for example
十二指肠系统（例如）中解释
gonadal
性腺
erythrocyte
红细胞
thymic, I need to address that
胸腺，我必须去那里
and you can already see it; from the palate, it is visible at the level of the testicles, just as
你们已经看到了，从上颚可以看到它在睾丸处，就像
it is seen
我们看到
in the pregnant woman, these are white lines; it is visible at the level of the sternum, which
在怀孕的女性身上，有白线，我们看到它在胸骨处，它
comes to close, the first contact that closes anteriorly on the
会闭合，第一次接触会闭合在前面，在
anterior plane will be a
前平面上会是一个
contact that will occur at the level of the angle of Louis; the angle of Louis is the meeting
接触，它会在路易角处发生，路易角是
of my
我的
manubrium sternum with the two small protuberances of the manubrium, the sternal bars
胸骨柄与胸骨柄的两个小球（胸骨条）的相遇
sternal and the ramp
胸骨条和斜坡
meeting, will form the angle of Louis, which is the global expression
相遇，将形成路易角，它是我的屈曲的整体表达。
of my flexion.
我的屈曲。
Therefore, this angle of Louis contains in its memory, in its
所以这意味着路易角在其记忆中，在其
expression
形成
of its formation, the history of my flexion.
的表达中，包含了我的屈曲的历史。
At the moment this anterior phase closes, a specific formation will occur
当我在这里前面有这个闭合阶段时，我将有一个
specific
特定的
here, at the level of my mediastinum.
形成，它发生在我纵隔的这个位置。
In other words, the sternal angle (of Louis) represents the dynamic equilibrium
换句话说，路易角是动态平衡。
of the definitive formation of my mediastinum.
我的纵隔最终形成的动态平衡。
Whereas the xiphoid process, when its formation is completed,
而剑突，当它结束时，
occurs much later,
发生得晚得多，
will occur simultaneously
将同时发生
with the integration of my cecum
我的盲肠整合
into the right iliac fossa,
在右髂窝中，
which represents the terminal phase
这是最终阶段
of the definitive positioning
我的结肠框架的
of my colonic frame.
最终就位。
At one point, it was a small embryo.
在某个时刻，它是一个小胚胎。
And it performed a flexion movement, like this.
它做了一个这样的屈曲运动。
Anteriorly, during this flexion,
在这里前面，在这个屈曲的时候，
all the tissue integrates anteriorly. So here,
所有的组织都向前整合，所以在这里
anteriorly, we will observe that these are
前面我们会看到这是
the sternal bars, and when the sternal bars, along with the manubrium, converge during this flexion,
胸骨条，当胸骨条和胸骨柄在这个屈曲中
they will meet, leading to an anterior densification. At the moment of this densification,
相遇时，会有一个前方的致密化，当我有这个致密化时
this convergence represents the equilibrium of my mediastinum, meaning
这次相遇代表着我的纵隔平衡，
the cardio-pleuro-
也就是说，心肺胸膜空间，
pulmonary space, okay, with the
肺部等等，开始就位，好的，然后随着
time, this continues here, and later there will
时间的推移，它会继续在这里，然后它会
be what we call the xiphoid process; its formation occurs much later. The
稍后会出现我们所说的剑突，这会晚得多，
intestine,
肠道
during its development, performs a counterclockwise rotation of 270 degrees.
在其发育过程中，它会进行逆时针旋转，一个270度的运动，
As this descends to form my entire sternum, including the sternal angle,
当它下降形成我的整个胸骨和路易角时，
my intestine also descends.
我的肠子下降了。
here, initially, it is located there and then descends
它最初在这里，然后下降。
into the right iliac fossa, the cecum integrates, and once fully integrated into
进入右髂窝，盲肠整合，当它完全整合到
the iliac fossa—that is, even postnatally—the final manifestation is observed
髂窝中时，也就是说，甚至在出生后，我看到了最终的结果
here, at the xiphoid process.
在这里，剑突点。
This implies that the xiphoid process represents the dynamic equilibrium of
这意味着剑突点代表了
the definitive establishment
结肠框架最终就位
of the colonic framework within the definitive right iliac fossa, specifically the cecum.
在右髂窝中，我的盲肠最终就位。
Because at a certain point, it undergoes elongation, and this is where it integrates into the definitive iliac fossa,
因为在某个时刻，它会伸展，这就是它与窝结合的地方。
yet it necessitates both flexion and longitudinal growth
最终的，但我需要我的屈曲和纵向生长
for elongation.
来伸长
This does not occur solely through flexion; rather, it involves the totality of movement, which subsequently entails
这不仅仅发生在屈曲中，它发生在整个运动中，这是一个
a movement of iteration of sternal deformations, indicating equilibrium in movements
胸骨变形的重复运动，它显示了平衡和运动
whether of
无论是
a genetic organizational type, meaning we receive transgenerational information
遗传组织类型，也就是说，我们接收到跨代信息
e.g., 'like my father, I also have this thoracic configuration,' or 'like my mother, I have a notched thorax,'
我像我父亲一样，胸部也是如此，或者像我母亲一样，胸部有缺口
etc. Alternatively, it may sometimes indicate calcium-related deficiencies that can
等等。或者有时它显示钙水平的缺陷，它可能
occur. This entire
有。所有这些
anti-clockwise intestinal developmental movement, which is
肠道发育的运动，以逆时针方向进行
highly specific,
非常具体，
organized by a mesenteric vascular axis, which we will simultaneously contextualize within the
由肠系膜血管轴组织，我们将同时将其置于
movement of the brain, while concurrently, the upper limbs are developing. Therefore,
大脑的运动中，同时您将进行上肢运动。所以
we will learn to re-engage with the 'Tai Chi of the brain,' followed by the 'Tai Chi of the intestine,' and then
我们将学习重新做大脑的太极，然后我们将做肠道的太极，然后
subsequently,
然后
the 'Tai Chi of the upper limb.' This implies that phenomena observed here could be the expression
上肢的太极，所以这意味着这里可能发生的事情可能是
of an imbalance on a purely cerebral or purely digestive plane. Flexion,
纯粹的大脑或纯粹的消化系统失衡的表达，屈曲
relative extension,
相对伸展
but also extension and elongation, because the overarching process is
但是伸展和拉长，因为大的过程是
one of coiling, but also of lengthening.
我卷曲，但我也伸长
You see, and I straighten within this movement.
你看到了吗？我在这场运动中挺直了身体。
all lines, all anterior forces converge towards
所有的线条，所有的前部力量都汇聚到
anteriorly.
向前。
So I first start from my notochord where I have the wave.
所以我首先从我的脊索开始，那里有波浪。
This wave creates my neural tube.
这个波浪形成了我的神经管。
And this neural tube will lead all the material to develop anteriorly
而这个神经管将带动所有物质向前发展，
in relation to the growth and straightening of the embryo.
与胚胎的生长和直立相关。
So first, I have this wave, then I have my neural tube,
所以首先，我有这个波浪，然后我有我的神经管，
and then...
然后……
will create the folding. So the midline creates the posterior midline which creates
将形成卷曲。所以中线形成了后中线，后中线形成了
the anterior midline, which becomes an axis of positional probability again,
前中线，它又成为一个概率定位轴，
because I have, for
因为我有，例如，
example, the creation of my red blood cells, my gonads, it's all that brings me anteriorly.
我的红细胞和性腺的形成，所有这些都引导我向前。
And sometimes you have people, they are blocked in their life initiation. Initiated,
有时你会遇到一些人，他们被困在生命的起始阶段。起始，
that means
意味着他们开始，
that they start, that they can start. And you have this line and sometimes you have
他们可以开始。你看到这条线，有时你会在这条线上发现密度，我称之为……
densities on this line, areas of what I call...
我称之为……
of time and sometimes I will look for a blockage on this line, I look for a knot,
时间，有时我会在那条线上寻找一个堵塞，我寻找一个结，
a
一个
densification and I will release this knot. There is a way to release these knots, to
致密化，然后我会释放这个结。有一种方法可以释放这些结，
unravel these
爆发这些
knots and you re-release the possibility, the probability of the person. So you understand
结，然后你重新释放了那个人的可能性，那个人的概率。所以你明白
that it is a kinetic biodynamics of developing growth, in relation
这是一种动力学胚胎学，是生长发育的动力学，与
with
我的大脑相关，与我的力线相关，这些力线将在团队层面被发现。
my brain, in relation to my lines of force that we will find at the level of the team.
在我的轴线上，既有Urmérien轴，也有我的鳃弓，
level of my axes, both Urmerian and my branchial arches, that
所有这些都反映在
on this famous sphenobasilar synchondrosis which, do not forget, is a fulcrum in the
那个著名的蝶枕结合上，别忘了，它在发育阶段是一个支点。
phase of development.
发育阶段的支点。
Remember this phase of development here, at the level of my notochord, where
回想一下这里，在我的脊索水平的这个发育阶段，
finally I have this wave of development with my zero point, that is to say the
最终我有了这个发育波，我的零点，也就是说，
point
不动点
immobile and the point of Hensen's node, which migrates through space, giving rise to
和恩森结的移动点，它在空间中移动，将形成
the
在德语中，有一个词是这样说的，先驱力量，为了
arrive at.
达到。